Guide to the Norton Nicholls Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1750 Jun 27
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Nion. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1794 Sep 8 (Box 6, Folder 574)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cornwall. Concerns family, 1794 Sep 8 (Box 6, Folder 575)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cornwall. Concerns gardening, 1794 Sep 28 (Box 6, Folder 576)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cornwall., 1794 Sep 8 (Box 6, Folder 577)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Heligan., 1794 Oct 8 (Box 6, Folder 578)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Plymouth., 1794 Oct 16 (Box 6, Folder 579)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Plymouth., 1794 Oct 23 (Box 6, Folder 580)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ipswich., 1794 Dec 25 (Box 6, Folder 581)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1794 Dec 28 (Box 6, Folder 582)
  - [H. Hudson] to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London, [1794?] (Box 6, Folder 583)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1795 Jan 2 (Box 6, Folder 584)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; family business, 1795 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 585)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1795 Jan 30 (Box 6, Folder 586)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1795 Feb 7 (Box 6, Folder 587)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; France, 1795 Feb 14 (Box 6, Folder 588)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1795 Feb 19 (Box 6, Folder 589)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1795 Feb 28 (Box 6, Folder 590)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1795 Mar 10 (Box 6, Folder 591)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1795 Mar 14 (Box 6, Folder 592)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1795 Mar 21 (Box 6, Folder 593)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1795 Mar 30 (Box 6, Folder 594)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1795 Apr 1 (Box 6, Folder 595)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1795 Apr 4 (Box 6, Folder 596)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1795 Apr 13 (Box 6, Folder 597)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1795 Apr 18 (Box 6, Folder 598)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1795 Apr 23 (Box 6, Folder 599)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1795 Apr 27 (Box 6, Folder 600)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1795 May 1 (Box 6, Folder 601)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1795 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 602)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business; Indian affairs; music, 1795 May 13 (Box 6, Folder 603)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1795 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 604)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1795 Jun 20 (Box 6, Folder 605)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Raynam., 1795 Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 606)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1796 Mar 13 (Box 6, Folder 607)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London; music, 1796 Jul 11 (Box 6, Folder 608)
  - W[illiam] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Felbrigg. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1796 Jul 25 (Box 6, Folder 609)
  - Jane Floyer Nicholls to Alexander Wedderburn, Earl of Rosslyn. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1796 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 610)
  - Jane Floyer Nicholls to Alexander Wedderburn, Earl of Rosslyn. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1797 (Box 6, Folder 611)
  - Jane Floyer Nicholls to Alexander Wedderburn, Earl of Rosslyn. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1797 Apr 3 (Box 6, Folder 612)
  - Unidentified to Norton Nicholls. Cornwall. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1796 Sep 7 (Box 6, Folder 613)
  - J[oseph] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Earlham Hall. Concerns literature, 1796 Nov 12 (Box 6, Folder 614)
  - J[oseph] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Earlham Hall. Concerns literature, 1796 Dec 4 (Box 6, Folder 615)
  - W[illiam] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Earlham Hall. Concerns literature, 1796 Dec 12 (Box 6, Folder 616)
  - Bentruch to Norton Nicholls. n.p., [1796] (Box 6, Folder 617)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milton. Concerns Cambridge University, 1797 Jan 8 (Box 6, Folder 618)
  - Elisabeth Turner to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Bath., 1797 Jan 15 (Box 6, Folder 619)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milton. Concerns Cambridge University; Augustus Floyer, 1797 Jan 16 (Box 6, Folder 620)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milton. Concerns Cambridge University, 1797 Jan 22 (Box 6, Folder 621)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milton., 1797 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 622)
  - Augustus Floyer to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1797 Feb 6 (Box 6, Folder 623)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park, Concerns London; music, 1797 Feb 5 (Box 6, Folder 624)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park, Concerns Indian affairs, 1797 Feb 10 (Box 6, Folder 625)
  - A. M. Floyer to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Bifrens., 1797 Feb 11 (Box 6, Folder 626)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1797 Feb 17 (Box 6, Folder 627)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Feb 21 (Box 6, Folder 628)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family health, 1797 Feb 24 (Box 6, Folder 629)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Mar 2 (Box 6, Folder 630)
  - Norton Nicholls to Maria. London. Concerns London, [1797 Mar 8] (Box 6, Folder 631)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1797 Mar 15 (Box 6, Folder 632)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Mar 21 (Box 6, Folder 633)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Mar 27 (Box 6, Folder 634)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; Augustus Floyer, 1797 Mar 31 (Box 6, Folder 635)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1797 Apr] (Box 6, Folder 636)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Apr 8 (Box 6, Folder 637)
  - Augustus Floyer to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Scotland, 1797 Apr 28 (Box 6, Folder 638)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London; family, 1797 Apr 29 (Box 6, Folder 639)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1797 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 640)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 May 20 (Box 6, Folder 641)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 642)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1797] (Box 6, Folder 643)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; Augustus Floyer, 1797 May 29 (Box 6, Folder 644)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1797 Jun 6 (Box 6, Folder 645)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns family business, 1797 Jun 10 (Box 6, Folder 646)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1797 Jun 14 (Box 6, Folder 647)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns Charles de Bonstetten, 1797 Jun 19 (Box 6, Folder 648)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. Navy Pay Office. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1797 Jun 29 (Box 6, Folder 649)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1797 Jul 3 (Box 6, Folder 650)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns J. F. Erskine, 1797 Jul 12 (Box 6, Folder 651)
  - George Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milton. Concerns family, 1797 Jul 16 (Box 6, Folder 652)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns family, 1797 Jul 18 (Box 6, Folder 653)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1797 Jul 25 (Box 6, Folder 654)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1797 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 655)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1797 Aug 16 (Box 6, Folder 656)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1797 Aug 19 (Box 6, Folder 657)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Winslade. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1797 Sep 3 (Box 6, Folder 658)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Andover., 1797 Sep 13 (Box 6, Folder 659)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park., 1797 Sep 16 (Box 6, Folder 660)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park., 1797 Sep 25 (Box 6, Folder 661)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park., 1797 Sep 29 (Box 6, Folder 662)
  - John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield to Norton Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield; literature, 1797 Oct 2 (Box 6, Folder 663)
  - George Nicholls to Norton Nicholls. Milton. Concerns Cambridge University; family business, 1797 Oct 16 (Box 6, Folder 664)
  - Norton Nicholls to George Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns Norton Nicholls; mentions father, 1797 Oct 19 (Box 6, Folder 665)
  - Louis Nicole to Norton Nicholls. London., 1797 Nov 10 (Box 6, Folder 666)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1797 Nov 19 (Box 6, Folder 667)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson; literature, 1797 Nov 25 (Box 6, Folder 668)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1797 Nov 29 (Box 6, Folder 669)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1797 Dec 5 (Box 6, Folder 670)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1797 Dec 11 (Box 6, Folder 671)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Augustus Floyer, 1797 Dec 16 (Box 6, Folder 672)
  - Mrs. Anderson to Norton Nicholls. London., [1797?] (Box 6, Folder 673)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1797 Dec 23 (Box 6, Folder 674)
  - Anderson to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London; John Wheler, 1797 Dec 30 (Box 6, Folder 675)
  - Cecilia Johnston to Norton Nicholls. Hampton., 1797 Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 676)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1797 Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 677)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1798 Jan 6 (Box 7, Folder 678)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rainham., 1798 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 679)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey. Concerns gardening, 1798 Jan 23 (Box 7, Folder 680)
  - Cecilia Johnston to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns John Wheler, 1798 Jan 27 (Box 7, Folder 681)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, 1st Earl of Sheffield; Augustus Floyer; family business, 1798 Jan 29 (Box 7, Folder 682)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns William Bligh, 1798 Feb 6 (Box 7, Folder 683)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns London, 1798 Feb 12 (Box 7, Folder 684)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1798 Feb 20 (Box 7, Folder 685)
  - Mrs. Anderson to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns music; family business, 1798 Feb 23 (Box 7, Folder 686)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns William Bligh, 1798 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 687)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music; family business, 1798 Mar 5 (Box 7, Folder 688)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns William Bligh, 1798 Mar 4 (Box 7, Folder 689)
  - Mrs. Anderson to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns music; Napoleonic wars, [1798] Mar 15 (Box 7, Folder 690)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Suffolk, 1798 Mar 20 (Box 7, Folder 691)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1798 Mar 29 (Box 7, Folder 692)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1798 Apr 3 (Box 7, Folder 693)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Joseph Windham, 1798 Apr 6 (Box 7, Folder 694)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Earsham. Concerns Joseph Windham, 1798 Apr 12 (Box 7, Folder 695)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1798 Apr 19 (Box 7, Folder 696)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1798 Apr 25 (Box 7, Folder 697)
  - Mallet du Pan to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London; Charles de Bonstetten, 1798 May 16 (Box 7, Folder 698)
  - C. Jerningham to Norton Nicholls. London., 1798 Jun 22 (Box 7, Folder 699)
  - Norton Nicholls to George Townshend, Earl of Leicester. n.p. Concerns France, 1798 (Box 7, Folder 700)
  - Sir Francis Freeling to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1798 Aug 4 (Box 7, Folder 701)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns literature, 1798 Aug 6 (Box 7, Folder 702)
  - Anne Powlett to Norton Nicholls. Winslade., 1798 Aug 19 (Box 7, Folder 703)
  - T. Clarke to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns family business, 1798 Aug 24 (Box 7, Folder 704)
  - Lally Tollendal to Norton Nicholls. Richmond., 1798 Aug 29 (Box 7, Folder 705)
  - T. Clarke to Norton Nicholls. Mells. Concerns literature, 1798 Sep 3 (Box 7, Folder 706)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1798 Sep 11 (Box 7, Folder 707)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. London, 1798 Sep 20 (Box 7, Folder 708)
  - Anne Powlett to Norton Nicholls. Winslade. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1798 Oct 22 (Box 7, Folder 709)
  - Mallet du Pan to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Charles de Bonstetten, 1798 Oct 27 (Box 7, Folder 710)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns William Johnson Temple., 1798 Nov 13 (Box 7, Folder 711)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Palgrave., 1798 Dec 2 (Box 7, Folder 712)
  - Norton Nicholls to Lady Beauchamp. Blundeston., 1798 Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 713)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1798 Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 714)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Grundisburgh. Concerns family, 1799 Jan 12 (Box 7, Folder 715)
  - [Charles de Bonstetten?] to Norton Nicholls. Bern, Switzerland. Concerns Switzerland; literature, 1799 Jan 12 (Box 7, Folder 716)
  - Duncan to Norton Nicholls. n.p., [1799 May 16] (Box 7, Folder 717)
  - J. F. Erskine to Norton Nicholls. Alloa. Concerns family business, 1799 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 718)
  - C. Johnson to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament; George Townshend, Earl of Leicester., 1799 Jun 15 (Box 7, Folder 719)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Hungerford Park. Concerns sermons, 1799 Jul 7 (Box 7, Folder 720)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Corsham House., 1799 Jul 15 (Box 7, Folder 721)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Salisbury. Concerns family business, 1799 Jul 22 (Box 7, Folder 722)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Bevis Mount., 1799 Jul 29 (Box 7, Folder 723)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1799 Aug 25 (Box 7, Folder 724)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns family, 1799 Sep 3 (Box 7, Folder 725)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1799 Sep 17 (Box 7, Folder 726)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1799 Sep 24 (Box 7, Folder 727)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns family business, 1799 Oct 2 (Box 7, Folder 728)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1799 Oct 8 (Box 7, Folder 729)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Copenhagen. Concerns Bern, Switzerland; literature; Copenhagen, 1799 Oct 12 (Box 7, Folder 730)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1799 Dec 11 (Box 7, Folder 731)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1799 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 732)
  - S. Douglas to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns pheasantry; gardening, 1799 Dec 15 (Box 7, Folder 733)
  - Richard Troward to Norton Nicholls. Norfolk. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1799 Dec 19 (Box 7, Folder 734)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1799 Dec 20 (Box 7, Folder 735)
  - Norton Nicholls to Richard Troward. Blundeston. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1799 Dec 20 (Box 7, Folder 736)
  - Richard Troward to Norton Nicholls. Norfolk., 1799 Dec 23 (Box 7, Folder 737)
  - Frederick Hamilton to Norton Nicholls. Richmond., 1799 Dec 24 (Box 7, Folder 738)
  - Norton Nicholls to Richard Troward. Blundeston. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1799 Dec 26 (Box 7, Folder 739)
  - [George] Wollaston to Richard Troward. n.p. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1800 Jan 5 (Box 7, Folder 740)
  - Norton Nicholls to George Wollaston. Richmond. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1800 Jan 7 (Box 7, Folder 741)
  - George Wollaston to Thomas Onslow, Earl of Onslow. n.p. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1800 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 742)
  - Norton Nicholls to George Wollaston. n.p., 1800 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 743)
  - Norton Nicholls to George Wollaston. n.p. Different hand from 743, 1800 Jan (Box 7, Folder 744)
  - T. Roope to Norton Nicholls. Yarmouth. Concerns music, 1800 Jan 23 (Box 7, Folder 745)
  - Mallet du Pan to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns family; death of Jane Floyer Nicholls, 1800 Jan 27 (Box 7, Folder 746)
  - Anne Sheffield (North) Holroyd, Countess of Sheffield to Norton Nichols. Whitehall., 1800 Feb 1 (Box 7, Folder 747)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Copenhagen. Concerns Bern, Switzerland; Copenhagen, 1800 May 1 (Box 7, Folder 748)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Copenhagen. Concerns Copenhagen; France, 1800 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 749)
  - Joseph Windham to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Thomas Gray, 1800 Dec 6 (Box 7, Folder 750)
  - N. Molls to Norton Nicholls. Cambridge., 1801 Feb 18 (Box 7, Folder 751)
  - George Nicholls to Norton Nicholls. Cambridge. Concerns family business, 1801 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 752)
  - Anne Sheffield (North) Holroyd, Countess of Sheffield to Norton Nicholls. Mitchell., 1807 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 753)
  - George Nicholls to Norton Nicholls. Cambridge. Concerns death of Jane Floyer Nicholls, 1801 Jun 16 (Box 7, Folder 754)
  - William Wentworth, Earl Fitzwilliam to Norton Nicholls. Richmond., 1801 Oct 24 (Box 7, Folder 755)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Jun 6 (Box 7, Folder 756)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Jun 11 (Box 7, Folder 757)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Jun 13 (Box 7, Folder 758)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Jun 29 (Box 7, Folder 759)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Jul 10 (Box 7, Folder 760)
  - John Casamajor to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett; Roman Catholicism, 1802 Jul 29 (Box 7, Folder 761)
  - Robert Reeve to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns Suffolk, 1802 Sep 16 (Box 7, Folder 762)
  - Robert Reeve to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns Suffolk, 1802 Sep 18 (Box 7, Folder 763)
  - T. Barrett to Norton Nicholls. Lee., 1802 Oct 16 (Box 7, Folder 764)
  - Octavius Temple to Norton Nicholls. Winchester. Concerns family business, 1802 Oct 19 (Box 7, Folder 765)
  - William Windham to Norton Nicholls. Felbrigg., [1802?] (Box 7, Folder 766)
  - T. D. Boswell to Norton Nicholls. Navy Pay Office. Concerns Octavius Temple, 1802 Nov 9 (Box 7, Folder 767)
  - George Chamberlayne to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett; Norton Nicholls, 1802 Nov 18 (Box 7, Folder 768)
  - George Chamberlayne to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Nov 28 (Box 7, Folder 769)
  - Robert Reeve to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns Suffolk, 1802 Nov 30 (Box 7, Folder 770)
  - George Chamberlayne to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Dec 6 (Box 7, Folder 771)
  - George Chamberlayne to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1802 Dec 16 (Box 7, Folder 772)
  - George Chamberlayne to Norton Nicholls. Lee. Concerns T. Barrett, 1803 Jan 10 (Box 7, Folder 773)
  - Edward Austen to Norton Nicholls. Godmersham Park. Concerns T. Barrett, 1803 Jan 10 (Box 7, Folder 774)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1803 Feb 5 (Box 7, Folder 775)
  - Thomas Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Yorleston. Concerns William Douglas, Duke of Queensbury, 1803 Aug 26 (Box 7, Folder 776)
  - George Boston (Irby), Baron Boston, to Norton Nicholls. Hudson Lodge. Concerns family, 1803 Sep 10 (Box 7, Folder 777)
  - Augustus Floyer to Alexander Grant. Madras. Concerns Indian affairs, 1803 Sep 27 (Box 7, Folder 778)
  - Chadworth to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns literature, 1803 Sep 28 (Box 7, Folder 779)
  - George Boston (Irby), Baron Boston, to Norton Nicholls. Hudson Lodge. Concerns Suffolk, 1803 Oct 11 (Box 7, Folder 780)
  - Thomas Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Bradwell. Concerns advowson, 1803 Oct 14 (Box 7, Folder 781)
  - Thomas Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Hopton. Concerns advowson, 1803 Nov 24 (Box 7, Folder 782)
  - Charles Berners to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Suffolk; advowson, 1803 Dec 6 (Box 7, Folder 783)
  - William Wentworth Fitzwilliam, Earl Fitzwilliam to Norton Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns literature, 1803 Dec 22 (Box 7, Folder 784)
  - William Wentworth Fitzwilliam, Earl Fitzwilliam to Norton Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns Thomas Onslow, Earl of Onslow, 1804 Jan 13 (Box 8, Folder 785)
  - George Hardinge to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Cambridge University, [1804] (Box 8, Folder 786)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1804 Jan 15 (Box 8, Folder 787)
  - John Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Hopton. Concerns clergy; Suffolk, 1804 Apr 2 (Box 8, Folder 788)
  - Anne (North) Holroyd, Countess of Sheffield to Norton Nicholls. Clifton. Concerns Norton Nicholls; Samuel Johnson, 1804 Apr 6 (Box 8, Folder 789)
  - Dawson Turner to Norton Nicholls. Yarmouth. Concerns gardening, 1804 Apr 15 (Box 8, Folder 790)
  - Thomas Dann to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns Suffolk, 1804 May 29 (Box 8, Folder 791)
  - Joseph Bonomi to Sir Thomas Gooch. London., 1804 Jun 12 (Box 8, Folder 792)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1804 Jul 1 (Box 8, Folder 793)
  - Dawson Turner to Norton Nicholls. Yarmouth., 1804 Jul 4 (Box 8, Folder 794)
  - John Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Bradwell. Concerns gardening, 1804 Oct 29 (Box 8, Folder 795)
  - Thomas Thurtell to Norton Nicholls. Bradwell. Concerns advowson, 1804 Nov 1 (Box 8, Folder 796)
  - Norton Nicholls to Charles Manners-Sutton, Archbishop of Canterbury. Blundeston. Concerns clergy, 1805 Feb 18 (Box 8, Folder 797)
  - Robert Reeve to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns advowson; Suffolk; Napoleonic wars, 1805 Mar 24 (Box 8, Folder 798)
  - Philip Stanhope, Earl of Chesterfield to Norton Nicholls. Stratford Place. Concerns music, 1805 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 799)
  - George Cambridge to Norton Nicholls. Twickenham., 1805 May 21 (Box 8, Folder 800)
  - Robert Reeves to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns family business; Suffolk; Napoleonic wars, 1805 Jun 25 (Box 8, Folder 801)